Subtitles by explosiveskull
[ KING CRIMSON 'S " STARLESS " PLAYS ]
♪ Sundown ♪
♪ Dazzling day ♪
♪ Gold ♪
♪ Through my eyes ♪
♪ But my eyes ♪
♪ Turned within ♪
♪ Only see ♪
♪ Starless and ♪
♪ Bible black ♪
♪ Old friend ♪
♪ Charity ♪
♪ Cruel ♪
♪ Twisted smile ♪
♪ And the smile ♪
♪ Signals emptiness ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ Starless and ♪
♪ Bible black ♪
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
RONALD REAGAN : There 's a great spiritual awakening in America .
A renewal of the traditional values
that have been the bedrock
of America 's goodness and greatness .
An overwhelming majority of Americans
disapprove of pornography , abor ...
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF , KEYS JINGLE ]
Knock , knock .
You scared the hell out of me .
- Knock , knock . - Who 's there ?
Erik Estrada .
Erik Estrada who ?
Erik Estrada from " CHiPs . "
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
What are you drawing ?
Uh , it 's kind of like , um , jungle temple .
Oh , that 's ... that 's ... I mean , that 's ...
Wow .
How was your day ?
MANDY : It was pretty cool .
I was reading that book about the galaxy .
That big , thick one ?
Yeah . It 's pretty awesome .
What 's your favorite planet ?
Jupiter .
Yeah , no doubt .
How come ?
Mm ...
Well , because the surface of its atmosphere
is a storm that 's been raging for , like , 1,000 years ,
and the eye of the hurricane is so huge
that it could just swallow the whole Earth .
Yeah . That 's ... That 's my favorite planet .
- That 's wild . - Mm-hmm .
What 's yours ?
Um ...
Saturn , probably .
Yeah ?
Saturn 's pretty cool ,
and that was one of the first ones that we discovered ,
that humans discovered , so there 's , like ,
a lot of cool ancient myths about it and stuff .
I changed my mind .
What ?
I like Galactus .
Galactus isn 't a planet .
Yeah , but he eats planets .
Woof . Woof , woof , woof .
[ BIRDS CHIRPING , ANIMALS CALLING ]
[ STATIC HISSING ]
Hey . Are you awake ?
Yeah , baby . What is it ?
You were having a bad dream .
Uh-huh .
What was it about ?
I can 't remember .
Sometimes I wonder if we should move away from this place .
Where ?
I don 't know .
No .
I like it here .
It 's peaceful here , right ? This is , like , our little ...
This is our little home .
Did I ever tell you about the starlings
when I was a little kid ?
No . I don 't think so .
In the neighborhood where I grew up ,
there were all these starlings flying around in the trees ,
playing and chirping , and they were so cute .
But my dad
he just hated them
' cause they were always eating cherries from the cherry tree .
Anyway , one day ...
One day , me and a bunch of the other kids from the neighborhood
were playing in this empty lot .
And my dad came walking across with a pillowcase
and a crowbar .
And there was something moving around inside of the pillowcase ,
like , squirming around .
And he said we should gather ' round .
He had something to show us , and so we all gathered ' round ,
and he emptied what was in the pillowcase on the ground .
And it was a ...
It was a bunch of baby starlings .
And he told us that he was gonna show us how to kill them .
And he lifted the crowbar up real high
and then
brought it down real hard on the little baby bird .
So hard that it pushed it in the ground .
It was so deep in there , like a little grave , you know ?
And then he gave the crowbar to one of the kids , and then ...
each kid took a turn in ...
killing a starling .
What 'd you do ?
I , um
just watched , and then when it was my turn , I just ran away .
Oh , baby .
Come here .
MANDY : " Under the crimson , primordial sky
surrounded by the jagged rocks
of the ancient volcanic mountain ,
the wretched Warlock
reached into the dark embrace of the fissure
until his hand touched a smooth glassy surface .
Cold as ice .
His fist closed around The Serpent 's Eye .
Slowly he withdrew it and held it before him
in the fading light of the blood-red suns .
It glowed from within .
A ghostly emerald light .
Strange and eternal . "
[ TV PLAYING IN DISTANCE ]
What 's the matter , Jeremiah ?
Are you all right ?
No .
I 'm not all right .
Did I do something wrong ?
Wrong ?
Everything you do is wrong .
I 'm so sorry , Jeremiah .
Is there anything I can do to make you feel better ?
There is nothing you can do .
It 's her .
I feel naked without her .
Naked .
Do you hear me ?
I-I ...
I said , " Do you hear me ? "
Yes , Jeremiah . I hear you .
" Yes , Jeremiah .
I hear you . " Really ?
Because , sometimes , I don 't think you hear anything at all .
And I am truly worried about that .
If you are not with me , you will not ascend .
- MARLENE : Jeremiah , I ... - Please ...
just be quiet and go fetch me Brother Swan .
Okay .
I said , " Go fetch me Brother Swan . "
There you are .
What can I do for you , Jeremiah ?
I need you to get me that girl I saw .
I need her .
I need her now .
Jeremiah , consider it done .
Do you have the Horn of Abraxas ?
Do you know what to do ?
I do .
Hey .
Why don 't we offer up the porker , too ?
Just to seal the deal .
That is such a good idea .
That lard-ass , he couldn 't find his nose in a mirror .
[ LAUGHS ]
I knew I could count on you .
I can always count on you .
Buddy .
Oh , thank you , Jeremiah .
Thank you .
Before you go
send in Sister Lucy .
BROTHER SWAN : Of course .
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
MARLENE : That 's a cool T-shirt .
Oh , thanks .
What you reading ?
MANDY : A novel .
Oh .
How do you like it ?
Yeah , I think it 's Lenora Tor 's best book .
Hmm .
I guess you live around here .
Yeah . We live just down near Crystal Lake .
Oh , that sounds lovely .
It 's 5 bucks .
Oh , yeah .
Well ...
See you later .
[ FOOTSTEPS DEPART ]
[ DOOR OPENS , BELL JINGLES ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
MAN : Are you sure this is the right place ?
BROTHER SWAN : Yes . Of course I am .
[ SCRAPING ]
[ VAN DOOR OPENS ]
[ HORN BLOWING ]
What now ?
Now we wait .
[ WINDOW WHIRRING ]
How long ?
Shh .
Listen .
[ ENGINES RUMBLING ]
[ BREATHING RAGGEDLY ]
[ SNARLING ]
[ CLICK ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ CLANK ]
[ VAN DOOR OPENS ]
[ VAN DOOR CLOSES ]
[ VAN DOORS CLOSE , CLANG ]
[ SNIFFS ]
[ JAR OPENS ]
[ GULPING ]
Blood for blood .
More .
First things first .
Aah !
Aaaah !
MAN : Jerry ? Jesus Christ .
- What the hell is that ? - I don 't know .
Oh !
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
[ ELECTRICITY BUZZING ]
[ SNARLING ]
[ GASPING ]
[ ELECTRICITY BUZZING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
MARLENE : Don 't worry .
Those scary men are gone now .
They got what they came for , and they 're gone .
I guess you 're wondering where your hubby is .
Don 't you worry . He 's just fine .
And he 'll stay that way as long as you 're a good girl
and do as you 're told .
- [ SLAP ] - [ MUFFLED GROAN ]
MARLENE : Do you understand me ?
You know , he thinks you 're so special ,
and I hope you realize what that means .
The responsibility is on you , buster .
[ GROANS ]
[ MOANING ]
MARLENE : Open .
[ MANDY GROANING ]
MARLENE : Very good .
Very good .
Hold still .
[ MANDY GROANING ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAMING ]
[ MOANING ]
I like to call that the cherry on top .
It 's all but a beautiful dream .
A dream he 's having right now .
Won 't you join us in that dream ?
I 'm sorry for all this fuss and muss .
But when I saw you on the road the other day
you called out to me
silently .
And I listened .
Look at me .
[ ECHOING ] Look at me !
Tell me .
What do you see ?
I see the reaper fast approaching .
Well , I recognized you ,
so I think in time
you will recognize me .
You know ,
all he wants is for his children
to love one another .
Now , I find that he allows me
to express that love in many ways ,
but one of those ways
is music .
Do you like the Carpenters ?
I think that they 're sensational ,
but this is even better .
[ CRACKLING ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
What do you think ?
[ MOANS ]
Shh . Shh . Wait .
It 's about to start .
♪ Every seed that gives us life ♪
♪ Every man must take a wife ♪
♪ Only one sun ever shines ♪
♪ Only one sun , yours and mine ♪
♪ Jeremiah Sand was a righteous man whose heart ... ♪
You know , I was ready to stand tall
with the great , grand glittery ones ,
but those scumbags couldn 't recognize
a golden , radiant light
even as it was cast right down upon them .
But thankfully ...
Thankfully , he showed me another path .
The path I have always been truly destined for ,
something far greater than mere fame or fortune .
♪ ... lessons well ♪
♪ The light shines through everything ♪
♪ The light is true , the lessons learned ♪
♪ His song of you and me ♪
When I was at the bottom of the pit
screaming in the darkness
racked with unspeakable pain
for having been denied all that was rightfully mine
he graced me with his light .
His hot loving light .
It flowed over me like the pulse of a timeless wave .
A wave of pure heat .
A mainline of pure and total acceptance .
And he talked to me .
Addressed me as a friend .
He said , " Jeremiah , they were wrong .
And you are right .
So right . "
And he blessed me with his holy kiss .
He said , " You are not separate from all that is .
So all that is
is yours . "
And he gave me his deepest and warmest permission
to go out into this world
and take what is so very much mine .
All of it .
Mine .
My wants .
My needs .
My pleasures .
[ INDISTINCT SINGING ]
You know
I 've been blessed to know the comfort of many women .
But there are few that have had your radiance .
You 're a special one , Mandy .
I , too , am a special one .
Let us be so very special together .
Be gentle
like me .
They ...
You made this song ?
Yes .
I did .
And it 's about you ?
Yes .
It is .
[ LAUGHING ]
Shut up !
[ LAUGHING CONTINUES ]
Shut up ! Shut up !
Shut up ! Shut up ! Shut up !
[ LAUGHING CONTINUES ]
Don 't you fucking look at me !
Don 't look at me ! Don 't you fucking look at me !
Don 't look at me !
[ LAUGHING CONTINUES ]
[ CRYING ] Tell me what to do .
Please tell me what to do .
Come on . Tell me what to do .
Tell me what to do . Tell me . Tell me .
Tell me what to do . Tell me what to do .
Tell me . Tell me .
Don 't ever doubt yourself .
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
You and that ugly little whore .
You think you 're so in love ?
I 'll show you love .
Lucy .
[ WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY ]
Kneel .
[ CLICK ]
Now show him how much you love me .
RED : No . [ GRUNTING ]
No .
[ GUN CLICKS ]
JEREMIAH : Another pearl wasted before swine .
BROTHER SWAN : Yeah .
Take a good look , you worthless piece of human excrement .
This is the tainted blade of the pale knight ,
straight from the abyssal layer .
Poor , stupid pigs .
Born without souls .
[ RED GRUNTS ]
You know what Jesus ' big mistake was ? Huh ?
He didn 't offer up a sacrifice in his stead .
The cruciform is a constant reminder of that .
[ SCREAMS ]
Now , we wasted the chemist 's finest on your whore .
But I think that you both
shall see the cleansing power of fire
cannot be reasoned with .
[ MATCH STRIKES ]
The darker the whore , the brighter the flame .
[ CAR DOOR CLOSES , ENGINE STARTS ]
[ CAR DOOR CLOSES ]
[ VAN DOOR OPENS ]
[ VAN DOORS CLOSING ]
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
[ VAN DOOR OPENS ]
[ VAN DOOR CLOSES ]
[ CAR DEPARTS ]
[ GROANING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANING ]
[ GRUNTS , PANTING ]
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ON TV ]
GIRL : Who ate all the macaroni and cheese ?
Cheddar Goblin , did you eat all the macaroni and cheese ?
CHEDDAR GOBLIN : Nothing 's better than cheddar .
GIRL : Cheddar Goblin .
[ CHILDREN CHEERING ]
ANNOUNCER : Cheddar Goblin by Duvane
has 60 % more cheese than the next leading brand .
Kids and goblins agree , Cheddar Goblin tastes the best .
That 's why Cheddar Goblin was rated number one
three years in a row .
Cheddar Goblin by Duvane . It 's gobblin ' good .
Cheddar Goblin .
MAN : This is a test .
This station is conducting a test
of the Emergency Broadcasting System .
This is only a test .
[ TONE BUZZING ]
[ MOANS ]
[ GASPS , BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ GROANING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ CRYING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ DOG BARKING ]
MAN : Can 't you read ?
Oh , it 's you .
It 's been a while .
Come for the Reaper .
MAN : Perfect condition , just like you left it .
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ON TV ]
I 'll get out of your hair .
MAN : So what you going to do with that thing ?
I 'm going hunting .
If you 're gonna go hunting ,
I got some other shit you might need .
I was hoping you 'd say that .
One to the right .
Made it myself .
It cut through bone like a fat kid through cake .
They 're yours under one condition .
Oh , yeah ? What 's that ?
You put them to good use .
[ DOG WHIMPERING ]
So what you hunting ?
Jesus freaks .
[ CRYING ]
I didn 't know they were in season , man .
Yeah . Well ...
- MAN : Just tell me , man . - They lit her on fire !
They were weirdo hippie types .
Whole bunch of them .
And there was a muscle . It didn 't make any sense .
They were bikers and gnarly psychos and ...
Crazy evil .
MAN : Black Skulls .
Black Skulls .
Lookit , man .
For a while now , word 's been coming down from the big rigs
something dark and fearsome out there .
No one knows where they come from .
First , it was stories from the interstate .
Leaving truckers for dead , prostitutes vanishing ,
and gutted bodies on doorsteps .
And always the same .
Biker gang , black bikes .
Only seen at night .
Weird shit .
There 's stories that there was a chapter
than ran courier for a manufacturer of LSD .
Took a disliking to them and cooked them up a special batch ,
and they have never been right in the head since .
I seen them once from a distance .
What you 're hunting is rabid animals ,
and you should go in knowing that your odds ain 't that good ,
and you will probably die .
Don 't be negative .
Last I heard on the CB ,
they were spotted down near Spirit River .
When I seen them things , they were in a world of pain .
But you know what the freakiest part was ?
What 's that ?
They fucking loved it .
[ SIZZLING ]
[ CLANGING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ ENGINES REVVING ]
[ SNARLING ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ SNARLS ]
[ HUMMING IN DISTANCE ]
Aah !
[ GROANING ]
Ah !
That was my favorite shirt .
[ GRUNTING ]
[ HISSING ]
Ah !
You have a death wish .
[ CRYING ] I-I don 't want ... I don 't want to talk about that .
[ CRYING ]
You 're a vicious snowflake .
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ CLATTERING ]
[ SNARLING ]
[ GROWLS ]
Ah !
- Aah ! - [ ROARS ]
[ GROANING ]
Aah !
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
You ripped my shirt !
[ GRUNTING ]
- Ah ! - [ THUD ]
[ SNIFFING ]
[ CLATTERS ]
[ SNIFFS ]
Ah !
[ THUD ]
- [ ROARS ] - [ GRUNTING ]
[ SNARLING ]
She 's still burning .
- [ LAUGHS EVILLY ] - Aah !
She burns .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ DOWN-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
MAN : It 's cool , man .
[ NOTES PLAY ]
Jovan warrior sent forth from the eye of the storm .
Mm .
That 's Lizzie .
When she 's calm , I know it 's good .
You 're right .
Oh ...
God . You 're right .
Bye , Lizzie .
Oh , man . They wronged you .
Why they got to be like that ?
You exude a cosmic darkness .
Can you see that ?
Okay .
The children .
North .
[ GROWLING ]
[ SNORING ]
[ WATER FLOWING ]
[ CHAINSAW BUZZING IN DISTANCE ]
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
[ AIR HISSES ]
[ VAN STOPS ]
This is really not ideal .
[ GRUNTS ]
You 're hurting me !
[ GAGS ]
She ... She burned brightly , Mandy .
Don 't you think ?
Still , better to burn out than fade ...
[ SQUISH ]
[ GAGGING ]
[ GURGLING ]
[ SQUISH ]
[ " CIELITO LINDO " PLAYS ]
[ MAN SINGING IN SPANISH ]
[ SCRAPING ]
[ BLOWS ]
[ MOTOR WHIRS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ CHAINSAW BUZZING ]
[ MOTOR WHIRS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CHAINSAW BUZZING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GRUNTING ]
Ah !
[ CHAINSAW BUZZING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ MAN LAUGHING ]
[ CHAINSAW BUZZING ]
[ GROANING ]
- [ SQUISH ] - [ SCREAMING ]
[ CHAINSAW BUZZING ]
[ WOMAN CRYING ]
Jeremiah says
I 'm the most sensual lover
he 's ever experienced
because of my sensitivity
and my empathy .
I can anticipate my lover 's every move .
I meet them .
Like warm waves
licking ...
the rocky ...
hard shore .
JEREMIAH : Come no closer .
God is in this room .
Aah !
Oh .
Hi .
You can 't harm me , man .
I mean , look at what he provides .
It 's all mine .
You 're just meat .
Without a soul .
Without a brain .
Without anything .
Animal .
You ...
You have no spirit everlasting .
No ...
No radiant light .
I possess hallucinations you will never know .
RED : The psychotic drones .
Where the mystic swims .
You 're drowning .
I 'm swimming .
You unholy abomination .
You aren 't even worth my spit .
It 's all that hate in your heart .
That 's to blame .
Follows you everywhere , man .
Follows you everywhere .
I can still help you .
It 's not just your life I can save , no .
It 's your goddamn soul .
No , no , no , no ! Please , please .
Please don 't hurt me !
Shh !
Can 't you see this was all part of your journey ,
the journey that led you to me ?
To your salvation .
To your cleansing by my hand .
[ CRYING ]
I 'll blow you , man .
I 'll suck your fucking dick !
Is that what you want ?
Oh , please , please , please !
Please don 't do it .
No , no !
I don 't kneel before you !
You kneel before me !
I carry God 's gift in my heart , not you ,
so you kneel before me , motherfucker !
I 'm your god now .
[ GROANING ]
Aah ! [ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ THUD ]
[ CLATTER ]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]